<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><Planets><planet name="Caladan"><GFX><exterior>oceanic.png</exterior><space>M01.png</space></GFX><pos><y>0</y><x>0</x></pos><general><bar>
The bar is just off the starport with a great view of the harbour.  You could watch the fishermen run frantically about attending their duties for hours.
</bar><description>
The surface of the planet is predominantly covered with water and the planetary climate is characterised by abundant precipitation and strong winds, yet tolerable enough to make special and expensive weather control measures unnecessary. Habitable land is often characterised by soft meadows, swamps and dense forests. The resource base of Caladan consists mainly of agriculture and biomass, with the locally bred and grown pundi rice being its main export, and fishing a traditional source of sustenance for its people. Other traditional products include wine and various livestock, most prominently cattle. Cuisine on Caladan is rather refined, with most dishes containing meat.
</description><faction>Independent</faction><commodities><commodity>Food</commodity><commodity>Ore</commodity><commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity><commodity>Medicine</commodity></commodities><tech><main>3</main></tech><services>31</services><class>A</class></general></planet><planet name="New Haven"><GFX><exterior>gas.png</exterior><space>D00.png</space></GFX><pos><y>0</y><x>0</x></pos><general><bar>The Slop and Grill is one of the nastiest taverns in the universe.  The food and drink doesn't exactly help.  Most of it is brewed on New Haven and wouldn't pass any of the minimal health insurance tests.  Some of the booze even doubles as ship fuel if needed, which says a lot about the quality.
The clients are also deep space thugs, pirates, contrabandiers, mercenaries and othe shady folk that insist on keeping the ground coated with blood and broken teeth.  Not a great place to bring the family.</bar><description>New Haven is a small planet located beyond the boundries of law and justice.  Founded by Bartax the Great, one of the most successful pirates to ever live after the old Haven was annihilated.
The planet is mostly covered by very toxic gases and has a lot of radiation if you stray from the stronghold.  These very features are what made the Empire qualify it as uninhabitable as it doesn't have any strategic resources.  It's distance from other civilized worlds also gives it a nice cover from prying eyes.</description><faction>Pirate</faction><commodities><commodity>Medicine</commodity><commodity>Luxury Goods</commodity><commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity></commodities><tech><main>13</main></tech><services>31</services><class>D</class></general></planet><planet name="Selphod"><GFX><exterior>snow.png</exterior><space>P00.png</space></GFX><pos><y>0</y><x>0</x></pos><general><bar>Great bar if you like your drinks cold.</bar><description>Cold place.</description><faction>Empire</faction><commodities><commodity>Food</commodity><commodity>Ore</commodity><commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity></commodities><tech><main>0</main></tech><services>7</services><class>P</class></general></planet><planet name="Omega Station"><GFX><exterior>station00.png</exterior><space>000.png</space></GFX><pos><y>0</y><x>0</x></pos><general><bar>
The Omega Canteen is a dark place that seems calm, although everytime a robotic drone approaches an alarm sounds sending pilots to man their ships to  fight off the menace.
</bar><description>
Built to defend the Empire from the Collective.  The Omega Station has been the observer of countless battles fought in it's sector.  It's helped keep a stalemate in the sector.
</description><faction>Empire</faction><commodities><commodity>Food</commodity><commodity>Medicine</commodity></commodities><tech><main>5</main></tech><services>15</services><class>0</class></general></planet><planet name="Darkshed"><GFX><exterior>station02.png</exterior><space>002.png</space></GFX><pos><y>-33</y><x>-57</x></pos><general><bar>
The Darkshed cantina is decorated with all sorts of odd artifacts that marked different tendencies in spaceship outfitting.
</bar><description>
Reknown for it's outfit market and shipyards.  Almost the entire Darkshed station is dedicated to trading outfits and ships.  Mercenaries and bounty hunters from all over the galaxy come here to see the newest enhancements available in the market.  This tends to also attract many of the shadier characters in the universe winding up with frequent fights where they test their newly bought outfits.
</description><faction>Independent</faction><commodities><commodity>Food</commodity><commodity>Ore</commodity><commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity><commodity>Medicine</commodity><commodity>Luxury Goods</commodity></commodities><tech><main>13</main></tech><services>31</services><class>0</class></general></planet><planet name="S72839"><GFX><exterior>station01.png</exterior><space>001.png</space></GFX><pos><y>0</y><x>0</x></pos><general><services>0</services><tech><main>0</main></tech><class>0</class><faction>Collective</faction></general></planet><planet name="Ozogo X"><GFX><space>J00.png</space></GFX><pos><y>17</y><x>23</x></pos><general><services>0</services><tech><main>0</main></tech><class>J</class></general></planet><planet name="Arrakis"><GFX><exterior>desertic.png</exterior><space>H00.png</space></GFX><pos><y>0</y><x>0</x></pos><general><bar>
The Arrakeen canteen is a shady place.  Many scoundrels and lowlifes make this their home to avoid notice from the universal police.
</bar><description>
Arrakis is a desert planet with no natural precipitation.
</description><faction>Independent</faction><commodities><commodity>Food</commodity><commodity>Ore</commodity></commodities><tech><main>4</main></tech><services>7</services><class>H</class></general></planet></Planets>