<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Planets>
 <planet name="Caladan">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>oceanic.png</exterior>
   <space>M01.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The bar is just off the starport with a great view of the harbour.  You could watch the fishermen run frantically about attending their duties for hours.</bar>
   <description>The surface of the planet is predominantly covered with water and the planetary climate is characterised by abundant precipitation and strong winds, yet tolerable enough to make special and expensive weather control measures unnecessary. Habitable land is often characterised by soft meadows, swamps and dense forests. The resource base of Caladan consists mainly of agriculture and biomass, with the locally bred and grown pundi rice being its main export, and fishing a traditional source of sustenance for its people. Other traditional products include wine and various livestock, most prominently cattle. Cuisine on Caladan is rather refined, with most dishes containing meat.</description>
   <faction>Independent</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Ore</commodity>
    <commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity>
    <commodity>Medicine</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>3</main>
   </tech>
   <services>31</services>
   <class>A</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="New Haven">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>gas.png</exterior>
   <space>D00.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The Slop and Grill is one of the nastiest taverns in the universe.  The food and drink doesn't exactly help.  Most of it is brewed on New Haven and wouldn't pass any of the minimal health insurance tests.  Some of the booze even doubles as ship fuel if needed, which says a lot about the quality.The clients are also deep space thugs, pirates, contrabandiers, mercenaries and othe shady folk that insist on keeping the ground coated with blood and broken teeth.  Not a great place to bring the family.</bar>
   <description>New Haven is a small planet located beyond the boundries of law and justice.  Founded by Bartax the Great, one of the most successful pirates to ever live after the old Haven was annihilated.The planet is mostly covered by very toxic gases and has a lot of radiation if you stray from the stronghold.  These very features are what made the Empire qualify it as uninhabitable as it doesn't have any strategic resources.  It's distance from other civilized worlds also gives it a nice cover from prying eyes.</description>
   <faction>Pirate</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Medicine</commodity>
    <commodity>Luxury Goods</commodity>
    <commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>13</main>
    <special>9009</special>
   </tech>
   <services>31</services>
   <class>D</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Zabween">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station00.png</exterior>
   <space>000.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The bar walls are covered with pictures of Empire soldiers fallen in the fight against Haven and piracy in general.  It has become a custom of the Empire to put pictures of the fallen from fighting piracy.  They are working on another addition to be able to fit more pictures.</bar>
   <description>Zabween is an old station.  It was first created as an outpost to fight piracy, but with the destruction of the Haven it has calmed down a lot.  Now it's more of a gigantic commercial center selling all sorts of goods.  It keeps a museum with all sorts of ships and weapons that were used in the final fight against Haven.</description>
   <faction>Empire</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Medicine</commodity>
    <commodity>Luxury Goods</commodity>
    <commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>9</main>
   </tech>
   <services>31</services>
   <class>0</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Tau Station">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station00.png</exterior>
   <space>000.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>54</y>
   <x>47</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The Tau Prime algae has a very strong stench which seems to envelope the bar completely.  The smell is soo strong you can actually taste it.  It doesn't taste nearly as good unprocessed. Most algae runners stop to grab drinks between runs to try to get the taste of the algae out of their mouth, although the usually use licor made out of processed algae to do that.</bar>
   <description>Tau Station was constructed with the sole purpose of exploiting the algae produced on Tau Prime.  Being a completely watery algae world with a very corrosive environment, it was deemed more profitable to build a space station then a city on the planet surface.   From the station windows you can see heavy algae collectors flying to and from the surface on their endless algae runs.</description>
   <faction>Empire</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <services>7</services>
   <class>0</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="S38729">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station01.png</exterior>
   <space>001.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <services>0</services>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <class>3</class>
   <faction>Collective</faction>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="S23491">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station01.png</exterior>
   <space>001.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <services>0</services>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <class>3</class>
   <faction>Collective</faction>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Torloth">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>mining.png</exterior>
   <space>G00.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The spaceport bar is carved into a rich mineral deposit giving the walls great reflections and colours.  The local drink are made partially with minerals giving all a rocky taste.</bar>
   <description>Torloth is a heavy mining planet.  It has rich ores and minerals in abundance with no local life forms to speak of.  It's one of the strongholds of the Nexus corporation housing some of their important ship factories.  Of course the bigger ships have to get built off planet.</description>
   <faction>Empire</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Ore</commodity>
    <commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <services>7</services>
   <class>G</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Selphod">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>snow.png</exterior>
   <space>P00.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>Most of the drinks served at the bar are served very warm with heavy infusions of all kinds of spices.  They are designed to give a lot of energy to keep the body warm when walking in the cold base.</bar>
   <description>Selphod is a very harsh and barren ice planet.  Most of the locals have never ventured outside the established bases.  The reason is that to be able to venture outside you have to wear really heavy thermal protection with a personal generator to keep the body temperature at optimal.  Even then, if the gear isn't worn properly the cold will quickly enter and kill the living being in less then a mTSU.</description>
   <faction>Empire</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Ore</commodity>
    <commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <services>7</services>
   <class>P</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Omega Station">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station00.png</exterior>
   <space>000.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The Omega Canteen is a dark place that seems calm, although everytime a robotic drone approaches an alarm sounds sending pilots to man their ships to  fight off the menace.</bar>
   <description>Built to defend the Empire from the Collective.  The Omega Station has been the observer of countless battles fought in it's sector.  It's helped keep a stalemate in the sector.</description>
   <faction>Empire</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Medicine</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>5</main>
   </tech>
   <services>15</services>
   <class>0</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Eiroik">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>methane.png</exterior>
   <space>J01.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>239</y>
   <x>73</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <services>1</services>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <class>J</class>
   <description>Eiroik used to be a mining planet under the Empire rule until the Collective wiped out the human colonies on it.  The harsh atmosphere did the rest, erasing all tracks of former human life.</description>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Darkshed">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station02.png</exterior>
   <space>002.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>-33</y>
   <x>-57</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The Darkshed cantina is decorated with all sorts of odd artifacts that marked different tendencies in spaceship outfitting.</bar>
   <description>Reknown for it's outfit market and shipyards.  Almost the entire Darkshed station is dedicated to trading outfits and ships.  Mercenaries and bounty hunters from all over the galaxy come here to see the newest enhancements available in the market.  This tends to also attract many of the shadier characters in the universe winding up with frequent fights where they test their newly bought outfits.</description>
   <faction>Independent</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Ore</commodity>
    <commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity>
    <commodity>Medicine</commodity>
    <commodity>Luxury Goods</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>13</main>
   </tech>
   <services>31</services>
   <class>0</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="S72839">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station01.png</exterior>
   <space>001.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <services>0</services>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <class>3</class>
   <faction>Collective</faction>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="S49281">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station01.png</exterior>
   <space>001.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <services>0</services>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <class>3</class>
   <faction>Collective</faction>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Zhiru">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>oceanic.png</exterior>
   <space>M04.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The Goddard Bar is unsurprisingly an old obsolete model remade as a bar.  It's surprisingly comfortable and  cozy as a bar, although every so often you can hear creaking in the ancient metal frame.</bar>
   <description>Zhiru es well known for being the birthplace of the Goddard.  Everything seems themed around the massive space vessel.  It was a quiet planet until the Goddard Inc. was created.  Now most of the population is employed by them.</description>
   <faction>Independent</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Ore</commodity>
    <commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>10</main>
    <special>1001</special>
   </tech>
   <services>31</services>
   <class>M</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Tau Prime">
  <GFX>
   <space>M02.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <services>0</services>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <class>M</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Ozogo X">
  <GFX>
   <space>J00.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>17</y>
   <x>23</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <services>0</services>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <class>J</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="S00000">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>station01.png</exterior>
   <space>001.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <services>0</services>
   <tech>
    <main>0</main>
   </tech>
   <class>3</class>
   <faction>Collective</faction>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Arrakis">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>desertic.png</exterior>
   <space>H00.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The Arrakeen canteen is a shady place.  Many scoundrels and lowlifes make this their home to avoid notice from the universal police.</bar>
   <description>Arrakis is a desert planet with no natural precipitation.</description>
   <faction>Independent</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Ore</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>4</main>
   </tech>
   <services>7</services>
   <class>H</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
 <planet name="Anecu">
  <GFX>
   <exterior>aquatic.png</exterior>
   <space>M03.png</space>
  </GFX>
  <pos>
   <y>0</y>
   <x>0</x>
  </pos>
  <general>
   <bar>The spaceport bar is aproximately 3 km below the surface of the planet.  Most of the walls are of a hardened transparet polymer that allows you to see into the darkness of the water.  Every so often you can notice a gelatinous creature slide around, barely illuminated by the bar lighting.</bar>
   <description>Anecu is a completely aquatic planet.  It's surface is covered completely by water.  In the shallow areas great underwater cities are constructed, as the climate above the water can be very harsh (waves been recorded to be up to 2 km high).  The planet boasts of extensive ship designing facilities, using the high pressure water as a testbed for ships of all sorts.</description>
   <faction>Empire</faction>
   <commodities>
    <commodity>Food</commodity>
    <commodity>Medicine</commodity>
    <commodity>Ore</commodity>
    <commodity>Luxury Goods</commodity>
    <commodity>Industrial Goods</commodity>
   </commodities>
   <tech>
    <main>9</main>
   </tech>
   <services>31</services>
   <class>M</class>
  </general>
 </planet>
</Planets>
