<ship name="Dvaered Ancestor Calamity" inherits="Dvaered Ancestor">
 <rarity>3</rarity>
 <price>850000</price>
 <cond>require("buyrep")("Dvaered", 40)</cond>
 <condstr>You need at least 40% reputation with House Dvaered.</condstr>
 <description>The Super-Fast Collider Launchers have more in common with most torpedo launchers than you'd think. All it takes for them to work just as well on a comparatively tiny bomber-class vessel is a redesign of its weapon mounts to be rigidly integrated with them. The newly possible generous design assumptions have also allowed for a substantial increase in targeting accuracy, much needed for better luck fighting off ships of its own caliber, but Dvaered technology can only be pushed so far, so the result is a ship much heavier yet less armoured than the original Ancestor, although bearing ridiculous firepower.
 
This design carries the legend of one empoverished Lord Calamares, who, as they say, lost their prized Goddard in a bet on the Crimson Gauntlet. Desperate to earn back their pride, they spent the last of their finances on second-hand launchers that barely fit on their last space-worthy ship, a Dvaered Ancestor, to threaten the very warlord they lost the jewel of their once-grand fleet to. Both perished in what passed for a fight, one that would be a footnote in history had it not been taken note of by a High Command officer, who would then order a refined design based on the doomed pilot's idea.</description>
 <health>
  <armour>50</armour>
 </health>
 <characteristics>
  <crew>6</crew>
  <mass>90</mass>
  <fuel_consumption>100</fuel_consumption>
  <cargo>6</cargo>
 </characteristics>
 <slots>
  <weapon prop="builtin" y="8" h="-1" size="large" x="-2">Super-Fast Collider Launcher</weapon>
  <weapon prop="builtin" y="-8" h="-1" size="large" x="-2">Super-Fast Collider Launcher</weapon>
  <utility prop="systems" name="systems" size="small">Unicorp PT-16 Core System</utility>
  <utility prop="systems_secondary" name="systems_secondary" size="small">Milspec Thalos 2202 Core System</utility>
  <utility prop="accessory" name="accessory" size="small"/>
  <utility size="small"/>
  <utility size="small"/>
  <utility size="small"/>
  <structure prop="engines" name="engines" size="small">Melendez Ox Engine</structure>
  <structure prop="engines_secondary" name="engines_secondary" size="small">Unicorp Hawk 160 Engine</structure>
  <structure prop="hull" name="hull" size="small">Unicorp D-2 Light Plating</structure>
  <structure prop="hull_secondary" name="hull_secondary" size="small">Unicorp D-2 Light Plating</structure>
  <structure size="small"/>
  <structure size="small"/>
  <structure size="small"/>
  <structure size="small"/>
 </slots>
 <stats>
  <cpu_mod>-25</cpu_mod>
  <speed_mod>-10</speed_mod>
  <shield_mod>-10</shield_mod>
  <ammo_capacity>30</ammo_capacity>
  <ew_track>30</ew_track>
  <engine_limit_rel>10</engine_limit_rel>
  <energy_regen_mod>-25</energy_regen_mod>
 </stats>
</ship>
