<spob name="Amletia">
 <pos x="-4671.021791" y="-3921.787683"/>
 <GFX>
  <space>M09</space>
  <exterior>aquatic2</exterior>
 </GFX>
 <presence>
  <faction>Yetmer</faction>
  <base>200.000000</base>
  <bonus>100.000000</bonus>
  <range>1</range>
 </presence>
 <general>
  <class>M</class>
  <population>5.3e+06</population>
  <hide>1.000000</hide>
  <services>
   <land/>
   <refuel/>
   <bar/>
   <missions/>
   <commodity/>
   <outfits/>
  </services>
  <description>Ceded to House Yetmer-O'rez and named after the first-born heir Amlet Yetmer-O'rez, Amletia was meant to be the secondary planet of the House, a safe place to raise children. However, after the intra-house war started, the local infrastructure has been forced to transition from luxurious housing and second homes to industrial infrastructure to support the war efforts. As can be expected, this has had a large toll on the quality of life on the planet over the long number of cycles that have passed since the fighting began. It is not uncommon for sirens to sound when enemy ships enter the system, but it seems like most people have gotten used to and mostly ignore them as they go about their business.

Ametlia was heavily hit during the beginning of the war, coming under siege by House O'rez. However, it was nearly miraculously overcome by a small fleet that was able to break the blockade and liberate the planet. The pilots are still revered as heroes to this day with a prominent statue at the space port. A lot of the damage done then is still visible throughout the planet surface.</description>
  <bar>What was once the Amlet Bistro has been replaced with a more practical Yetmer Cantina. The outer building is spectacularly lavish, however, half of the it has had to be replaced due to a near-direct hit by a bomb at the beginning of the war. The insides have been reinforced with ship panels to give more protection to the clients at a low cost. Usually, the bar is crowded with weary pilots between their patrol and attack shifts. The few non-locals tend to mind their own business as much as possible and leave as soon as they can.</bar>
 </general>
 <tech>
  <item>Beam 1</item>
  <item>Systems Elite (Za'lek)</item>
  <item>Engines Medium</item>
  <item>Port N Polish</item>
 </tech>
</spob>
