<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<spob name="Ivy Primary Hub">
 <pos x="500.000000" y="0.000000"/>
 <GFX>
  <space>station-cylinder.webp</space>
  <exterior>station05.webp</exterior>
 </GFX>
 <presence>
  <faction>Trader</faction>
  <base>66.666667</base>
  <bonus>33.333333</bonus>
  <range>1</range>
 </presence>
 <general>
  <class>M</class>
  <population>1e+05</population>
  <hide>1.000000</hide>
  <services>
   <land>land_hiclass</land>
   <refuel/>
   <bar/>
   <commodity/>
   <outfits/>
  </services>
  <commodities/>
  <description>Ivy Primary Hub is the centre of operations for one of the largest guilds in the galaxy, the Red Star Organisation. Originally organising humanitarian aid and rescue to the numerous half-failed and failed colonisations across the frontier and beyond, the Organisation then took on transporting water and food and medicines to more and more of the galaxy, then the Incident came and suddenly they were the most influencial people to know and the ones that everyone clamoured to to help them. In time their need decreased but they became the defacto traders of most food, water and medicines as well a producing many new treatments (many jointly with the Soromid). To not belong to the Organisation but tread on their turf risks your reputation and don't expect smiles when you visit their Head Quarters!</description>
  <bar>The spaceport bar is not shy about advertising exactly who runs the place, nor their accomplishments over the long and varied history of their claimed existance. Their red star motif is emblasoned across the walls between the murals depicting their heroic saving of colonies, refugees and the wounded of the various wars fought across the galaxy. Curiously abscent is their depiction of the sky high margins they make from being a near monopoly of water, food and medical trade between factions (though the ostentaciousness of the spaceport leaves that in little doubt!)</bar>
 </general>
 <tech>
  <item>Cargo Trader Outfits</item>
  <item>Crappy Core Systems</item>
  <item>Engines Cargo</item>
  <item>Hulls Cargo</item>
  <item>Basic Trade Ships</item>
  <item>Bulk Trade Ships</item>
 </tech>
 <tags>
  <tag>station</tag>
  <tag>old</tag>
  <tag>rich</tag>
  <tag>trade</tag>
 </tags>
</spob>
