<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<spob name="Wyrmwood">
 <pos x="-1397.724997" y="2373.913884"/>
 <GFX>
  <space>moon-P03.webp</space>
  <exterior>methane.webp</exterior>
 </GFX>
 <presence>
  <faction>Soromid</faction>
  <base>50.000000</base>
  <bonus>25.000000</bonus>
  <range>1</range>
 </presence>
 <general>
  <class>P</class>
  <population>795000</population>
  <hide>0.200000</hide>
  <services>
   <land/>
   <refuel/>
   <bar/>
   <missions/>
   <commodity/>
   <outfits/>
   <shipyard/>
  </services>
  <commodities/>
  <description>Wyrmwood is extremely well camouflaged in the asteroid field of Octantis, and for this reason it was only colonized fairly recently. Being surrounded and constantly pummeled by asteroids, one would think that Wyrmwood would not be able to sustain and develop life, however, it has significantly adapted and the ecosystem is based around nutrients and resources unearthed by the constant battering. The Soromid have also quickly adapted to life here and a rich and prosperous research community exists mainly in the depths of the oceans to minimise the risk of a direct asteroid impact. The locals are, in general, somewhat oblivious to the surrounding galaxy and are mainly focused on happenings at Wyrmwood.</description>
  <bar>The bar is extremely dimly lit as the locals have been genetically modified to have extremely sensitive low-light vision, although some hovering lamp globes can be borrowed by visitors that are not as well adapted. The atmosphere is very quiet which contrasts starkly with the occasional boom of an asteroid impact on the surface of the planet.</bar>
 </general>
 <tech>
  <item>Heavy Weapons 1</item>
  <item>High Tech Upgrades 3</item>
  <item>Plasma 2</item>
  <item>Plasma 1</item>
  <item>Star Maps</item>
  <item>Soromid Elite Outfits</item>
  <item>Systems Elite</item>
  <item>Systems High</item>
  <item>Engines Medium</item>
  <item>Engines High</item>
  <item>Hulls High</item>
 </tech>
 <tags>
  <tag>rich</tag>
  <tag>research</tag>
  <tag>new</tag>
 </tags>
</spob>
